お前さ　崎んとこの娘と結婚すんの
So... are you marrying Zaki's girl?
俺が
Me?!
Yeah. I just called him up, and he
started askin' me about a wedding date!
さっき崎に電話したら
なんか結婚式の具体的な日取りとか相談されてな
まっ　なんか酔ってるみたいだったが
He did sound kinda sloshed, though.
お前　星奈ちゃんと付き合ってんだろう
So, are you datin' Sena-chan?
O-Of course not!
なんだ　つまんねえな
Aw, bummer.
じゃ、彼女の一人ぐらいできたか
Do you at least have
your first girlfriend, then?
ねえよ
No.
友達もいないのに 彼女なんて
A girlfriend, when I don't
even have a friend-friend?
Huh? What did you say?
なんだって
Oh, hey, Kobato got a boyfriend.
She's staying at his place again tonight.
そういや　小鳩に彼氏ができたよ
今夜も外泊中
なんだと
What?! Who the hell is he?!
どこのどいつさ　俺の天使に手出しあがったこの野郎が
Who's the bastard who
made a move on my angel?!
だたじゃおかねえ　すぐに日本へ戻る
He's gonna pay! I'm comin'
back to Japan right now!
嘘だよ　そんじゃまたな
I was kidding. Okay, bye.
Huh? Hey, wait a...
おい　ちょっとま…
Be My Friend
BE MY FRIEND
Shiranai furi shitatte
知らないフリしたって
BE MYSELF
Be My Side
Zenbu kizuiteta yo
全部気付いてるよ
Mou ippo kimi no tonari ni ikou
もう一歩
君の隣に行こう
Sono te ni datte todokisou sa
その手にだって届きそうさ
"Haganai NEXT"
Souzou ijou da ne jetto koosutaa na mainichi
想像しちゃダメ
ジェットコースターな毎日
Hisshi de mae wo muite itsumo kakenuketa n da
引き締めて前を向いて
いつも駆け抜けたら
Zutto tsuzuki wa shinai ne bokura no jikan wa
ずっと続きはしないね
僕らの時間は今しかないから
Ima shika nai kara kono shunkan kizamitsukeyou
この瞬間刻みづけよう
Be My Friend
BE MY FRIEND
Shiranai furi shitatte
知らないフリしたって
Be My Side
BE MYSELF
Zenbu kizuiteta yo
全部気付いてるよ
Mou ippo kimi no tonari ni ikou
もう一歩
君の隣に行こう
受け止めるように
Te wo toreru you ni
Be My Friend
BE MY FRIEND
Miagete bakari datte
見上げてばかりだって
Be My Side
BE MYSELF
憧れてる今も
Akogareteru ima mo
Mou ikkai nando demo te wo nobasou
もう一回
何度でも手を伸ばそう
Ano hoshi datte todokisou sa
あの星だって届きそうさ
"A Man Is Among Them!"
Yo.
おす
Ah, Kobato-chan's here!
小鳩ちゃん来た
Bro...
あんちゃん
Kobato-chan, want to go to an
amusement park with me tomorrow?
小鳩ちゃん　明日私と一緒に遊園地に行きませんか
No!
いや
Look, look, it's a ticket
to Yokoshima Wonderland!
ほらほら　見て見て
Yokoshima Wonderland
Complimentary Shareholder Ticket
ヨコシマワンダーランドのチケットよ
Daddy got it from somebody
at work. And look at this!
パパが仕事先の人にもらったの
これも見て
Fullmetal Necromancer
Character Show!
There'll be limited-edition stuff there!
限定グッツもあるんだって
お菓子やおいしいハンバーグも食べさせてあげる
And I'll buy you snacks and a tasty hamburger!
Limited edition stuff... snacks... hamburgers!
限定グッツ　お菓子　ハンバーグ
Come on, Kobato-chan, don't be scared!
ほらほら　小鳩ちゃん　怖くないから
I'll be gentle! So have some
fun with your big sis! Okay?
優しくするから
だからお姉ちゃんと一緒に　ね
How pathetic can you get?
どこまで残念なのだ　貴様は
- Give it back, stupid Yozora!
- Yokoshima Wonderland, eh?
返しなさいよ　馬鹿夜空
ヨコシマワンダーランドか
Have you been there, Yozora?
夜空は行ったことあるのか
My school did a fall field
trip there in eighth grade.
中二の秋に学校の遠足でな
I spent the whole time reading a book, though.
ずっと本を読んで過ごしてたが
I-I see...
そうか
I've only been there with my family,
俺も家族としか行ったことないけど
but an amusement park with
friends sounds nice, you know?
友達と遊園地ってのは憧れるよな
Y-Yes...
そ　そうだな
All right, tomorrow we're all going
to Yokoshima Wonderland together!
よし　明日は皆でヨコシマワンダーランドへ行くぞ
For real?!
マジで
School's out, so we've all
got time to kill anyway, right?
どうせ試験休みで皆暇なのだろう
True.
まあな
And tomorrow is a weekday,
so it probably won't be crowded...
平日なので人も少なそうですし　理科も行きたいです
Rika wants to go too!
I shall accompany you, Aniki.
兄貴　わたくしも御伴いたします
Yay! I'm going to the amusement park!
わ～い　遊園地行く
お兄ちゃんとヨコシマワンダーランドへ行くぞ
- I'm going to Yokoshima
Wonderland with Big Brother!
- I suppose I'll divert myself with
a human pastime, just this once.
われもたまには人間の遊戯に興じてやるとしよう
Okay, it's decided.
よし　決まりだな
Hold it! I only invited Kobato-chan!
ちょっと待ってよ  あたしが誘ったのは小鳩ちゃんだけよ
This ticket admits six adults.
We're helping you make sure it's not wasted.
このチケットは大人6人分だ
せっかくだから
使ってやろうというんだ
Wait, six adults?
あれ　大人6人分
Yay! Yay!
Huh? I can't go? Because I'm a little girl?
私は行けないのか　幼女なので
Because you're a little girl.
幼女なので
Oh. Yeah, I'm just a little girl, after all...
そっか　私は所詮幼女だからな
Don't worry, I'm used to it.
気にしないでください
こういうの慣れてますので
I can shell out enough for one kid's ticket.
子供一人分ぐらい　あたしが出してあげるわよ
Really?!
本当か
ありがとうな　星奈　お前いいやつだな
Thanks, Sena! You're a good person!
Hey, Sena.
なあ　星奈
What?
何
Did you notice anything off
about the President yesterday?
昨日なんか変わったことなかったか　理事長の様子
Daddy?
Come to think of it, after
he gave me the park tickets,
そういえば私に遊園地のチケットくれた後
he suddenly got all happy
and started drinking sake...
急に機嫌がよくなって　お酒飲み始めたはね
Why?
何で
Beats me. All I could think
about was inviting Kobato-chan,
さあ　小鳩ちゃん誘うことで頭いっぱいだったから
so I don't really remember.
よく覚えてないわ
Oh.
そっか
Yeah, it must've just been drunken rambling.
やっぱ酔ったうえでの戯言だよな
Tomorrow will be great, won't it, Kobato-chan?
明日は楽しみね　小鳩ちゃん
No!
いや
Oh, you're so cute!
可愛い
はいはい　遊園地
Wow!
すげえ
So this is the fabled "amusement park."
ここが伝説の遊園地ですか
Huh...
It must be Sena's first time, too.
星奈も遊園地初めてなんだな
So, what ride should we go on fir... huh?
それじゃ　最初は何に乗…　あれ
This one.
これだ
Black Dragon!
ブラックドラゴン
マジで
F-For real?!
You want to go straight to the
Black Dragon? Are you crazy?!
いきなりブラックドラゴンって正気か
絶対乗るって決めてたの
I swore to myself that I'd ride this!
J-Just so you know, I didn't stay up
all night deciding whether to ride it!
べ　別にどれに乗ろうか徹夜で悩んでなどいないぞ
I just figured, since it's famous...
とりあえず名物らしいから
Just you wait, dragon of the night.
待っておれ　闇の竜よ
- The Black Dragon... That name
seems fitting for a true man.
- I wanna ride that one too!
黒き竜　真の男に相応しそうな名前です
私もそれ乗りたいぞ
Don't come crying to me later.
泣いても知らねえからな
Let’s go
Let's go!
Quite slow, isn't it?
ずいぶんとゆっくりだな
The ignorant masses down
there look like flecks of dirt.
下のほうにいる愚民共がゴミのようね
What's the matter, dark dragon?
Is this all you've got?
どうした暗黒竜よ　貴様の力はその程度か
Rika's being stimulated by the nice
vibrations, and she's starting to get a little hot!
程よい振動が刺激になって
なんだかいやらしい気持ちになってきました
Whoa... I'm not liking how high we are.
ちょ　この高さやばくないか
That's right, Black Dragon! Lead me
to the far reaches of time and... and...
さあ　黒竜　ブラックドラゴンよ
われを遥か時の最果てまでみち…　導かんとって
No, don't!
- Th-Th-There's something so wrong
with whoever thought up this ride!
- D-D-Do you think I'll let you
get away with doing this to me?!
こんな乗り物考えた奴は絶対可笑しい　死ね死ね　サディストサイコ野郎
あたしをこんな目に遭わせてただで済むと思ってんの
鉄の塊分際が ふざけすぎて殺すのよ　夜空
- Drop dead, you scum! Pervert!
- You're just a hunk of steel!
A toy! I'll freaking kill you!
You lied to me again, Yozora!
I'm gonna die from this!
夜空　お前また嘘ついたな
こんな絶対死んでしまう
- Stop, stop, go back!
I'll kill you! I swear I'll kill you!
- W-Wait, stop, really, please stop! Please!
やめろ 戻れ 本当にやめてください 本当にやめてください
Here it comes...
来たよ これ
- I'm gonna die! You rotten apples!
- Bro!
死んでまうやろ 腐ったミカンどもめ
あんちゃん
Fuck.
Fuck
- Shit! Meat Meat Meat
Meat stupid Meat shitty Meat!
- Too high too high too high too high!
くそ　肉肉肉　馬鹿肉 憎憎何もかも
- Poopy poopy poopy poopy poopy poopy!
- Stop saying poopy,
you poopy holy woman! Broooo!
うんこ　うんこ　うんこ
"Form itself is emptiness;
emptiness itself is form..."
Your face tells me just how bad
you want it, you planetary mass whore!
物欲しそうにしやがって地球オブザビッチが
すっかりメス犬の顔になってやがる
You look like a bitch in heat!
Universal gravitation streak of shit!
万有引力のビチクソ野郎
- Kodaka! Kodaka, Kodaka, Kodaka, Kodaka!
- Die die die! I swear
I'll curse you! Kodaka, help me!
助けて　小鷹
うんこ　うんこ
- Poopy poopy poopy... Yay, high!
- Bro! Bro!
あんちゃん　あんちゃん
"...up to and including no
field of mind-consciousness..."
You better ejaculate
faster than the speed of light!
光速をこえて射精が
- A pig who can't transcend space-time
might as well blow it in his pants!
- Rika's lost it!
理科が壊れた
H-How was it?
ど　どうだった
That was super fun!
面白かったな
Rika's head hurts. Can't remember...
Can't remember anything...
頭が痛いです
何も　何も思い出せません
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention please.
ご来場の皆様にご案内いたします
There will be a Fullmetal Necromancer
skit at 10:45 on the event stage.
10時45分より　多目的ステージにて
鉄のネグロマンサー着ぐるみショーが開催されます
We hope to see you all there shortly.
皆様 どうぞお越しくださいませ
Kobato-chan...
小鳩ちゃん
Want to go with me?
俺と一緒に行くか
Yeah! Let's hurry, Bro!
うん　早く行こう　あんちゃん
Kobato-chan, wait!
小鳩ちゃん　待って
Guess what, Kobato-chan? I just bought
all the Fullmetal Necromancer Blu-rays!
小鳩ちゃん　あたしね
この間クロネグのブルーレイを全部買ってみたの
The truth is, I'm a huge fan!
あたしってば実は結構クロネグマニアなのよね
Who's your favorite character?
小鳩ちゃんは誰が好き
Me, I like Mel-chan from season
two best! She's a one-off character, but...
あたしはね　二季で出てきたメルちゃんが一番のお気にいりなの
一話だけのゲストキャラだけど
- Meryl.
- Pardon?
メリル
Meryl. The phoenix tamer
from Season 2 Episode 8.
メリル　二季八話に出た不死鳥使い
エメロード・ミレーユ・フォン・リヴァレイシア・鳳の愛称はメリル
Emeraude Mireille von Livaraycia
Ohtori's nickname is "Meryl." Not "Mel."
メルではない
A-Ah, right, Meryl-chan.
そうそう　メリルちゃん
And she came back in Episode 5 of Season 3!
しかもメリルちゃんは三季の五話で再登場したのだ
Um, Kobato-chan...
あのう　小鳩ちゃん
Sena, she's a serious fanatic
when it comes to this show,
星奈　こいつクロネグに関してはがちでマニアだから
so if you don't know your stuff,
you'll only set her off more.
半端なことを言うと火に油を注ぐだけだぞ
Kodaka, why don't real-world conversations
come with options and save points?!
小鷹　何でリアルの会話には選択肢とセーブポイントがないの
Hi there, boys and girls!
Thanks for stopping by!
よい子の皆　遊びに来てくれてありがとう
A really great friend
came here today for you guys!
今日は皆のために　素敵なお友達が来てくれたの
That's right: it's Guernica-chan
from Fullmetal Necromancer!
そう　鉄のネクロマンサーのゲルニカちゃんです
Okay, let's all call her name together!
さあ　皆で一緒にゲルニカちゃんを呼んでみましょう
One, two...
せーの
My name is Astaroth! Guernica's
running late thanks to a trap I set!
わしの名はアリスタロス
ゲルニカはわしの罠のよって到着が遅れておるわ
I'm taking you hostage before she gets here.
今のうちにお前達を人質にしてやる
Oh no! Help!
助けて
Now, would one of you kids come
be a hostage with this young lady?
さって　誰かお姉さんと一緒に人質になってくれる子はいないかな
There's a great free gift waiting for
whoever lets me take them hostage!
人質になってくれた子には　後で素敵なプレゼントがあるぞ
Can't ask for more than that...
至れり尽くせりだな
Me!
はい　はいはい　あたしが人質になってあげるわ
Me, me! I'll be a hostage for you!
Wh-What are you doing?!
な　何やってんだよ お前
Don't worry, Kobato-chan,
I'll get the free gift for you, okay?
あたしがプレゼントもらってきてあげるから
待っててね　小鳩ちゃん
- Hey, are you serious?
- I don't care about a gift from this stupid show.
おいおい　本気か
こんなショーでもらえるものなど要らぬわ
- Of course!
- I don't care about a gift from this stupid show.
もちろん
えーと　お母さんはできれば遠慮していただけると
Er, we'd like to ask the mothers
in the crowd to let the kids go first.
Huh? "Mothers"?
お母さん
Fine, then I'll take a
child in her mother's place!
ではお母さんの代わりにお嬢ちゃんを人質にしてやる
何言ってんの　あいつら
- What are they talking about?
- Now, does anybody
else want to be my hostage?
さって　ほかに人質になってくれる子はいないか
- I think they're mistaking
you for Kobato's mother.
- Now, does anybody
else want to be my hostage?
お前　小鳩の母親だと思われてるんじゃないか
M-Me and Kobato-chan, mother and daughter?!
な　なんであたしと小鳩ちゃんは親子なのよ
- Th-That would mean my husband...
is you... now wouldn't it?!
- It looks like nobody's raising their hands!
そ　それじゃ　旦那さんは小鷹ってことになるじゃないの
That's not even funny!
冗談じゃないわ　まったくもう
Yeah, well, I wouldn't like that either!
俺だってそんなの　いやだっつうの
What's that supposed to mean?! Honestly...
いやだは何よ　まったくもう
- There's a great free gift waiting for
whoever lets me take them hostage!
- Could I ask you to come over?
よかったら　ちょっといいかな
- And I mean really great!
- Kobato-chan?
小鳩ちゃん
Watch your step, okay?
足元気をつけてね
Guernica-chan
Director - Masashi Kaido
Pretty cool that you got
the director's autograph, huh?
よかったな　監督のサインもらえて
Mm-hmm!
Guess you wouldn't have gotten
that if Sena hadn't raised her hand, huh?
それがもらえたのって　あの時星奈が手を挙げたお陰だよな
Tha... tha...
Hmm?
Tha-Thank... you...
あ　あり…がとう
K-Kobato-chan!
小鳩ちゃん
Oh, Kobato-chan's so
cute when she's feeling shy!
照れてる小鳩ちゃん　可愛い
I want to thank you, too. Thanks.
俺からもお礼言っとくよ
ありがとうな
I-I didn't do it for you or anything!
べ　別にあんたのためじゃないんだからね
It was for Kobato-chan.
小鳩ちゃんのためなんだから
And anyway, what was with
that hag and the horse-head jerk?!
ていうか　あの婆と馬野郎
U-Us, married? I mean, sheesh...
だ　誰が夫婦なの　まったくもう
Married... that's just dumb!
First you'd think "couple"...
夫婦と本当　馬鹿じゃないが
まずはカップル
What'd you say?
何だって
Nothing! Hmph!
なんでもないわよ
So, what were you guys up to?
で　お前らは何してたんだ
I sat on a bench and read my book.
ベンチで本を読んでいた
Rika went on the merry-go-round ten times.
理科はメリーゴーランドに十回ほど
I ate a hot dog! And popcorn, and a crêpe, and...
フランクフォルト食べた
あとポップコンとクレープと　あとなんだっけな
- ...what else, again?
- I'm sorry you felt like you had
to buy so much food, Yukimura.
悪いな　幸村
いろいろ出させちゃって
Nonsense, it was an honor to
look after your younger sister, Aniki.
滅相も御座いませぬ
兄貴の妹君のお世話　光栄です
Here you go.
お待たせしました
Yay, curry!
カレーだ
Curry looks like p...
かれーってまるでうん
Your life depends on your next words.
続きの言葉次第では殺す
Pretty tasty stuff.
うめえので好きです
よし
Good.
Anyway, what do we do after lunch?
それより飯食ったらどうする
I want to go on the Black Dragon again!
ブラックドラゴンまた乗りたいの
ブラックドラゴンはもう止めとこうぜ
I think we've had enough
Black Dragon for today. Right?
なあ
I-I'm completely up for another ride...
あ　あたしはもう一回乗っても全然平気なんだけどね
But I suppose we shouldn't
if you guys are scared!
あ　あんた達が怖いんじゃ仕方ないかな
Don't play tough, Meat.
That thing had you seconds from death.
強がるな　肉
死にそうになっていたくせに
Excuse me? Your knees were knocking.
あんたこそガタガタ震えたじゃないの
N-No they weren't!
そ　そんなことはない
"Noooo!"
いや
Your screams are perfectly
preserved in my memory.
あんたの悲鳴はあたしの頭の中にはっきり残ってるわよ
You're the one who was crying!
N-Not only that, you peed a little, didn't you!
泣いてたのは貴様のだろうが
それどころか　すこし漏らしてただろう
H-How did you...
なんで知…
まさか　本当に
W-Wait, you really did?
Of course not! That lame
coaster didn't scare me one bit!
そんなわけないでしょう
あんな­­ヘッポココースターなんて全然怖くなかったんだから
Then let's see you prove
it by going another round!
だったらもう一度乗って証明してもらおう
Bring it on! And you
have to ride too, obviously!
望むところよ
もちろんあんたも乗りなさいよね
Because my camera's gonna get
a photo of the tears on your face!
デジカメであんたの泣き顔　ばっちり撮影してあげるんだからね
Wait, did you bring a camera?
デジカメなんて持ってきていたのか
Oh yeah, hidden and ready.
ばっちり隠し持ってるわ
Why bother hiding it?
なぜわざわざ隠す
Um... Why should that matter?
いいじゃない　そこはどうでも
Yokoshima Wonderland
Big Brother, this way!
お兄ちゃん　こっち
We're way up high!
めっちゃ高いぞ
The people look like flecks of dirt.
人がゴミのようだ
Man, the Black Dragon really is extreme.
こうして見ると　やっぱりすげえな　ブラックドラゴン
Come to think of it, I wonder
what happened to Yozora and Sena.
そういや　夜空達はどうしたんだろう
It's been a long time since we split up.
Shall we meet up with them again?
別れてから大分経ちますし　そろそろ合流しますか
Aniki.
兄貴　発見しました
We've found them.
頭痛い
My head hurts...
I feel sick.
気持ち悪い
Wh-What the heck happened?
な　何があったんだ
乗った
We rode it.
Eight times.
8回
You rode the Black Dragon eight times?!
ブラックドラゴンに8回
夜空が負けを認めないから
Yozora wouldn't admit that she lost...
Meat wouldn't hurry up and die...
肉がさっさと死なないから
So who won, then?
それで　どっちが勝ったんですか
The battle's still going.
まだ勝負は付いてない
Come on, it's time for the ninth round...
そろそろ９回目　行くわよ
No, don't do it. You both fought bravely, okay?
もう止めとけ
お前らはよく戦ったよ
ここは引き分けってことで
So let's just call it a tie.
Not happening!
断る
Over my dead body.
死んでも嫌ね
- I'll never let Meat w...
- I'll never let Yozora w...
この肉にだけは
夜空にだけは
絶対負け…
See you in the waiting room at 4:00, then.
それじゃ　４時に待合室な
Men's Bath
Maria, why are you coming to the men's side?
マリア　なんで男湯に来るんだ
I don't wanna go with them.
They smell like vomit.
あいつらげぼくさいから一緒にお風呂入りたくないのだ
Oh. Well, I guess that's fair.
そっか　ならしょうがないな
Yeah! I'm gonna take
a bath with big brother!
うん　お兄ちゃんとお風呂入る
兄貴
Aniki.
I shall wash your back for you.
お背中をお流しいたします
No, I'm fine! I'll do it myself!
いいって　自分で洗う
I see I am useless to you...
In that case, I shall...
やはりわたくしは兄貴にとって不要な存在
斯くなる上は
Okay, fine, you can wash it! Please wash it!
わかった　流していい　流してください
I hear and obey.
ご下命承りました
Hold on to your sanity, Kodaka! He's a dude!
頑張れ　俺の理性
こいつは男だ
これがおちんちんというものか
So this is what a weenie looks like!
Bad girl. Give me back my towel.
こら　タオル返せよ
Hey, how come you have
that weird thing on you?
なんでこんな変なの付いてるのだ
"Weird"? All guys have these.
変なのって
男には付いてるもんなんだよ
How come Yukimura doesn't have one, then?
じゃあ　なんで幸村には付いてないのだ
Yukimura's a boy with no weenie! He's weird!
幸村は男なのにおちんちんついてなくて変だな
It's because I haven't matured enough.
わたくしまだ　未熟者ですゆえ
Huh?!
So will you grow one when you're mature?
未熟じゃなくなったら生えてくるのか
Yes. I shall work hard to be
a full-fledged man like Aniki.
はい　早く兄貴のような立派な男になれるよう精進いたします
I hope you get one soon!
早く生えてくるといいな
What are you guys sayi...
お前ら何
It's not there...
つ　つ　付いてない
兄貴　恥ずかしいです
Aniki... I'm embarrassed.
- Y-Yeah... I guess a kid this
cute... couldn't be a... guy...
- Which one next?
そうだよな　こんなに可愛い子が男の子わけないじゃないか
That one!
It's hard to believe that right away...
俄かには信じ難いですね
Excuse Rika for a moment.
ちょっと失礼します
Wait... Rika?!
理科
My lord, there is no mistaking it!
This is a woman you see before you!
殿　間違いありませぬ
こやつ女子で御座るぞ
だからそう言ってるだろうに
That's what I just told you...
Well, Rika has to check these things personally.
いや　やっぱり自分で確認してみないことには
Okay, now you convince
Yukimura of it. I didn't have any luck.
というわけで　理科
幸村の説得頼む
俺じゃ無理だった
こんな時だけ頼りにされても
Rika doesn't like that you only
rely on her at times like this...
Yukimura-ku... er, -san... This way, please.
幸村…さん　ちょっとこっちへ
Really?
True, my body doesn't have one of those...
確かに　そのようなものはわたくしの体には
Aniki, I'm afraid I am not a true Japanese man.
兄貴　わたくしは日本男児ではありませんでした
More like you're not a man, period.
日本男児っつうか　男子じゃねえよ
Ack, wait! Don't cry, Yukimura!
待って　泣くな幸村
I deeply apologize.
申し訳御座いません
Say, why did you think you were a boy?
なあ　なんでお前は自分のことを男だと思ってたんだ
Family circumstances.
家庭の事情で
Oh...
Wait, that's the end of the explanation?!
今ので説明終わり
Yes.
はい
I'm amazed nobody figured it out before.
よくこれまでばれなかったわね
Apparently a few people have
noticed and pointed it out to her before,
気付いて指摘した人はこれまでにも言ったみたいなんですが
but she says she paid them no mind.
言われても気にしなかったそうです
I-I see...
そうか
I'm amazed Rika managed to bring her around.
理科はよく説得できたな
Aniki...
兄貴
Am I still your sworn brother,
even though I'm not a boy?
わたくしが男子でなくても
わたくしは兄貴の舎弟でしょうか
Obviously! You'll always be my brother.
当たり前だ
お前はこれからも俺の舎弟だ
Yes, Aniki. I shall always
remain your devoted servant.
はい　兄貴
これからも兄貴にご奉仕いたします
What are you blushing for, Kodaka?
何赤くなってんのよ　小鷹
But oh dear, Yukimura's suddenly
starting to look really cute to me...
でもどうしよう
何か幸村のことが急に可愛く見えてきたわ
I might find her a little moe!
ちょっと萌えるかも
Moe?!
萌える
Sure... she's a pretty-girl maid!
だって美少女メイドよ
Shit, how could I have been so careless?!
くそ　私としたことが迂闊な
Here I thought he was just an oddball...
色物だと思っていたら
Hey... What's with you, Yozora?
どうしたの　夜空
She's cute and sweet and submissive!
可愛くて素直で従順だぞ
And a maid who'll be his servant
on top of that?! Give me a break!
しかもメイドでご奉仕だ
ふざけろ
もういやだ　本当付いてない
I can't take it... I have no luck!
なんでこううまく行かないんだよ
Why do things go so badly?!
They all look like normal
cute girls when they're asleep.
こうして寝てると
普通の可愛い女の子なんだよな　全員
Aniki...
兄貴
Hikatta hazu no ano hoshi
光ったはずの星
Mayotta kumo ga jama shite mienaku naru
迷った雲が邪魔して
見えなくなる
Nani wo shinjitara ii?
何を信じたらいい
Fuantei sugiru sekai de
不安定すぎる世界で
Sodatta takaramono kowashikaketeta
育った宝物壊しかけてた
Nakusu no ga kowakute
なくすのが怖くて
Fujouri datte tameiki tsuki
不条理だって
ため息つき
どうにかどうで足掻いてた日々
Torikago de agaiteta hibi
Onaji sora wo miageteta n da bokura wa
同じ空を見上げてたんだ
僕らは
Kimi no te wo nigitta
toki nigirikaeshite kureta ne
君の手を握った時
握り返してくれたね
Tsunagatta kono te wa
donna hane yori tsuyoi n da
繋がったこの手は
どんな羽より強いんだ
Tsubasa nante nakutatte motto takaku toberu kara
翼だってなくったって
もっと高く飛べるから
Kitto ima nara daijoubu
きっと今なら大丈夫
Oozora kagayaku hoshi wo tsukamou
大空輝く星を掴もう
まさかわたくしが女子だったとは思いませんでした
I never imagined that I was a girl.
美少年キャラの女子ばれは数あれど
It's not uncommon for a pretty-boy
character to turn out to be a girl,
ばれた本人はそれを言うパターンは理科も初めて見ました
but this is the first time Rika's
seen the girl herself say that line.
まったくだ　斬新ならいいってもんじゃねえぞ
Totally. Jeez, novelty isn't
necessarily a good thing, you know.
申し訳ありません
My apologies.
次回　「そんな遊びはいけません～君がいると世界観が乱れる～」
"That  Kind of Play Is Not Allowed... and...
My Worldview Is Disturbed When You Are Around"
Next time: "That Kind of Play Is Not Allowed...
and... My Worldview Is
Disturbed When You Are Around"!
君って誰のことなんでしょうね
I wonder who the "you" refers to?
お前だろ
ネタばれ
It's you.
A spoiler?!